{"data":[{"question":"Slightly over half of the population of El Paso, Texas, says both English and spanish.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has been never ","b":"important for ","c":"no significant ","d":"potential","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Has been never->has never been","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Hickories are medium to large trees common in eastern and the central areas of North America.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"depend on ","b":"shipping ","c":"of trade ","d":"countries","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Of trade-> trade","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Approximately one-third of all persons involved in adult education programs in 1970 were enrolled in occupational education course.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"often ","b":"ground up ","c":"added to ","d":"to elimination ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- To elimination-> to eliminate","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Natural adhesives are primarily of animals or vegetable origin.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Some nematodes ","b":"very tiny ","c":"it ","d":"to view ","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Very tiny-> so tiny","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"As a glacier melts, rocks, boulders, trees, and tons of dirt deposit.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"estimated ","b":"life expectancy ","c":"decade ","d":"drastically ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Drastically-> is drastically","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"American manufacturers depend on ocean shipping for most of trade with other countries.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"each ","b":"yards ","c":"wanted to ","d":"him","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Each-> every","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The root of the chicory plant is often ground up and added to coffee to elimination its bitterness.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have finished ","b":"the first ","c":"will read ","d":"the second one","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- The second one-> the second\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Some nematodes are very tiny that it is necessary to view them through a microscope.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"thorough ","b":"neatly","c":"so as to ","d":"good ","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Neatly-> neat","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"It is estimated that a scientific principle has a life expectancy of approximately a decade before it drastically revised or replaced by newer information.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"perpetually ","b":"backbiting ","c":"is ","d":"even ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Is->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"He was stopped each dozen yards by friends who wanted to congratulate him.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Like ","b":"speech","c":"general ","d":"degree ","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Like-> as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}